ABI TURNER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A graduate from the Command Shift coding bootcamp seeking a career change into Software Development. A strong enthusiasm and ability to learn new technologies at pace and a desire to utilise and expand skills as a developer. Proven prioritisation and communication skills with over six years experience in a retail leadership role.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer Student, 10/2022 - 05/2023 Command Shift

- Studied full-stack development using JavaScript and React to create front-end applications integrated to the back-end with API's. Worked with Express.js and PostgreSQL for back-end CRUD operations. Implemented test-driven development throughout each project using testing frameworks such as Jest and Mocha.
- Learned industry best practices and communicated with tutors and students through stand-ups, retrospectives and code reviews.
- Collaborated with students on group projects through mob and pair programming.

Store Manager, 07/2017 - Current Sainsburys, West Yorkshire

- Accountable the performance of both single and dual site convenience stores with an annual turnover of up to £4.3million
- Analysing data to identify trends and drive efficiency across locations to deliver key performance measures.
- Exercising strong leadership skills to deliver business change at pace across site teams.
- Effective time management and resource planning between multisite locations
- Responsible for individual store KPIs and risk management in store.
- Championing diversity and inclusion across the West Yorkshire region including leading the Mentoring Women in Leadership program.

Retail Manager, 07/2014 - 07/2017

Sainsburys, West Yorkshire

• Various retail management positions

EDUCATION

Diploma of Higher Education, BTEC Level 3 Animal Management, 2010 - 2012 Park Lane College Leeds Horsforth Centre - Distinction *



Halifax, England HX6



07572764861



turner.abi@gmail.com



https://github.com/Abi-Turner



https://www.linkedin.com/in/abi-turner94/

SKILLS

JavaScript

React

Node.JS

PostgreSQL

Express.js

Firebase

Docker

Test Driven Development

Jest

Mocha

React Testing Library

GitHub

Debugging

REST APIs

Agile Software Methodologies

PROJECTS

Pawfect Match

Web application made using React with an integrated API, Firebase Authentication and Firestore for users to create an account, find and save personalised recommendations for dog breeds.

Surreal Estate

Web application made using React linked to MongoDB where properties can be added, updated, and deleted.

Weather App

Weather forecasting app built with React that uses live data from an API to display a five-day forecast for a selected location.

INTERESTS

Guitar & Ukulele (playing for 15yrs) || **Gaming** || **Travelling** (most recent trip was to Australia 2023) || **Mentoring** (Mentor for Women in Sainsbury's)